[{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980309755,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":31037,"timeElapsed":108097},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980329634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":19878,"timeElapsed":127977},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980342657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":13021,"timeElapsed":141000},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980349753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":7094,"timeElapsed":148096},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980356338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":6582,"timeElapsed":154681},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980360034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3694,"timeElapsed":158376},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980363705,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3670,"timeElapsed":162048},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980373508,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":9801,"timeElapsed":171851},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980382034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":8523,"timeElapsed":180377},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980404274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":18990,"timeElapsed":202616},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980409466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":5191,"timeElapsed":207809},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980414922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5454,"timeElapsed":213265},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980418305,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3382,"timeElapsed":216648},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980421866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3559,"timeElapsed":220209},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980424058,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2191,"timeElapsed":222401},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980426290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2231,"timeElapsed":224633},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980433418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":7126,"timeElapsed":231761},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980437370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"12","question":"If you could wake up tomorrow having gained any one quality or ability, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":3951,"timeElapsed":235713},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980451977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":13318,"timeElapsed":250320},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980458914,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":6935,"timeElapsed":257257},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980462314,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3399,"timeElapsed":260657},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980465938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3623,"timeElapsed":264281},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980468091,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2151,"timeElapsed":266434},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980470362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2270,"timeElapsed":268705},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980480818,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10454,"timeElapsed":279161},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980487370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":6550,"timeElapsed":285713},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980491754,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4382,"timeElapsed":290097},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980496114,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"223","question":"What is the most unusual food you’ve ever eaten? Describe where and when you last had this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":4358,"timeElapsed":294457},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980507234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":9846,"timeElapsed":305576},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980510771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3535,"timeElapsed":309114},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980512906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2134,"timeElapsed":311249},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980516465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3558,"timeElapsed":314808},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980519681,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":3215,"timeElapsed":318024},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980521761,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2078,"timeElapsed":320104},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980524794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3032,"timeElapsed":323137},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980527930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3134,"timeElapsed":326272},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980530065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2134,"timeElapsed":328408},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980540538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":9232,"timeElapsed":338881},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980542945,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2405,"timeElapsed":341288},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980545097,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2151,"timeElapsed":343440},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980549689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4591,"timeElapsed":348032},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980552234,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2543,"timeElapsed":350576},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980554241,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2006,"timeElapsed":352584},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980556369,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2126,"timeElapsed":354712},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980558585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2215,"timeElapsed":356928},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980560441,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1854,"timeElapsed":358784},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980572074,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":10079,"timeElapsed":370417},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980574713,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2638,"timeElapsed":373056},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980576946,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2231,"timeElapsed":375289},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980579257,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2310,"timeElapsed":377600},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980581753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2494,"timeElapsed":380096},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980584106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2351,"timeElapsed":382449},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980587298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3190,"timeElapsed":385641},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980590498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3198,"timeElapsed":388841},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980594994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"105","question":"Do you want to have kids? If you already do, did you want kids before having them? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4494,"timeElapsed":393337},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980604763,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":8456,"timeElapsed":403106},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980606538,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1773,"timeElapsed":404881},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980612434,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5895,"timeElapsed":410777},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980616162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3725,"timeElapsed":414505},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980618858,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2693,"timeElapsed":417201},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980620753,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1894,"timeElapsed":419096},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980625851,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5096,"timeElapsed":424194},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980628346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2493,"timeElapsed":426688},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980630857,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"191","question":"Do you routinely watch sports? Do you have a favorite sport or team? If you had to choose a new team or sport to follow, what would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2511,"timeElapsed":429200},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980649298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":17183,"timeElapsed":447641},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980652570,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3269,"timeElapsed":450912},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980656265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3694,"timeElapsed":454608},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980658994,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2727,"timeElapsed":457337},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980662290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3295,"timeElapsed":460633},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980664601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2309,"timeElapsed":462944},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980668209,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3606,"timeElapsed":466552},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980673226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5015,"timeElapsed":471569},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980675905,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"185","question":"If you could add another month to the year and thereby prolong the season in which that month is inserted by an extra month, where would you insert the extra month? Come up with a name for this new month and describe the season you would be prolonging.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2678,"timeElapsed":474248},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980688602,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":11304,"timeElapsed":486945},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980690394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1790,"timeElapsed":488737},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980692170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1775,"timeElapsed":490513},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980693738,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1566,"timeElapsed":492081},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980696187,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2447,"timeElapsed":494529},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980697706,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1519,"timeElapsed":496049},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980700578,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2870,"timeElapsed":498921},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980705882,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5303,"timeElapsed":504225},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980707803,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1919,"timeElapsed":506146},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980709593,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"199","question":"What was something interesting you learned recently? This can be a fact or something you learned how to do. Describe how or where you learned this.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1789,"timeElapsed":507936},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980726851,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":16120,"timeElapsed":525194},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980729778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2925,"timeElapsed":528121},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980732898,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":3119,"timeElapsed":531241},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980735394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":2494,"timeElapsed":533737},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980737785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2390,"timeElapsed":536128},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980739850,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2063,"timeElapsed":538193},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980742667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":2816,"timeElapsed":541010},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980746465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":3797,"timeElapsed":544808},{"subjectID":"zeev3op3yp","prolificID":"6734a8294ced5912bd590a3e","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25bd5aaeb005d8fe886","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980749289,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"116","question":"If someone wrote and directed a movie about you, what parts of your life (for example, components of your personality, beliefs, background, and life experiences) should be part of it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":2823,"timeElapsed":547632}]